brochuremonster.com 2008-08-20

# Privacy-Policy Page

At brochuremonster.com, your privacy will be protected by adopting all possible measures. We assure you this.Kindly go through the following to know how we deal with the personal information collected from our visitors and customers.

**Gathering of personal information**

Brochuremonster.com will not collect personal information without your permission. You can browse brochuremonster.com without revealing any personal details.However, we do need some personal identifiable information to provide our services needed by you. This includes brochure purchasing and support.

**Using personal information**

The entire personal information gathered will be stored firmly using network firewalls and access control procedures which ensure no chances for any unauthorized access. Your information will be treated with utmost confidentiality and will be used solely by brochuremonster.com only for the purpose of business communication like providing support service and delivery.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We assure you that your personal information will be safe with us. Brochuremonster.com will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to third parties under any circumstances.

**Security**

Brochuremonster.com makes use of the most excellent practices to make sure that your online transactions are safe and your personal credit information is stored securely. However, brochuremonster.com will not be held responsible for any breach of security.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Brochuremonster.com reserves the right to make changes to this policy at its sole discretion. Any changes made in this content will be posted on this page.
